체스터스 밀은 평범한 마을이었다
JULIA: Chester's Mill is
a place like any other.
적어도 얼마 전까지는
At least it used to be,
수수께끼의 돔이
마을을 덮기 전까지는
until we were cut off
from the rest of the world
by a mysterious dome.
(cows bellowing)
투명하고, 부술 수도 없으며
Invisible, indestructible,
빠져나갈 수도 없다
inescapable.
완전히 갇혔어
We're trapped.
우리는 이 돔의 정체에 대해
전혀 모른다
JULIA: We don't know where it
came from or why it's here,
하지만 돔이 이 마을을
덮고 있는 상황에서
but now that we're all trapped
under the dome together,
숨길 수 있는 비밀은 없다
none of our secrets are safe.
-너네 엄마 왜 저러셔?
-당뇨병이 있으셔
What's wrong with your mom?
She's a diabetic.
내 물을 원한다면
OLLIE:
You want my water,
대가를 지불하게
you'll have to pay for it.
주니어가 절 대피소에
감금했었어요
ANGIE: Junior locked me
in his fallout shelter.
걔 이제 경관이에요
Junior's a cop now.
-누가 제 말을 믿겠어요?
-난 믿는다
Who's gonna believe my word?
I do.
필요한 물건을 좀
가져가야겠어
We're just gonna
take what we want.
안돼!
No!
야!
Hey!
(grunts)
로즈가 죽었어
BARBIE:
Rose is dead.
조와 노리가 동시에
돔과 접촉했기 때문이에요
JULIA: Joe and Norrie touched
the dome together.
쟤네 둘이 연관되어있어
They're connected to it.
내가 약속하마
BIG JIM:
I'm offering you my word.
주니어는 더 이상
널 건드리지 못할 거다
Junior Rennie will
never touch you again.
아빠
JUNIOR:
Dad.
앤지?
Angie?
(slow, filtered breathing)
조...
(echoing):
Joe...
조...
조!
Joe!
노리
(laughs)
Norrie.
안녕
Hi.
내 방에 온 걸 환영해
Welcome to my room.
나랑 같이 돔에 가 보자
I want you to come
with me to the dome.
비밀을 알아내 보자구
So we can figure all this out.
우리가 돔과 어떻게
연결되어 있는지
See how we're really
connected to it.
도디의 기계가
우리에게 신호를 잡아냈다고 해서
Just because Dodee's
gadget thing beeped at us
-우리가...
-들어봐
doesn't mean that...
Listen.
우리가 돔을 만졌을 때
이상한 일이 생겼잖아
Something happened
when we both touched it.
우리한테 뭔가 힘이
있는 것 같아
It was like we had
powers or something.
놀랍지 않아?
Don't you think that's amazing?
난 이런 말을 했던 건
아니었어
It's not exactly
the word I'd use.
이건 내 말이 맞아
Well, you should.
돔과 대화라도 할 수 있는지
가서 알아내보자구
Let's go see if we can
talk to it or something.
돔이 원하는 걸 듣고,
See what the dome wants,
사라지도록 설득해보자
and convince it to go away.
나 일단 바지 좀
갈아입으면 안 돼?
Can I get my pants on first?
나 꼭 나가야 돼?
Can I watch?
농담한거야
Kidding.
♪
안 돼요
No.
좀만 더 있어요
I'd like you to stay.
(knock on door)
갈 거에요
(whispers):
They will go away.
(knocking continues)
-해리엇
-안녕하세요?
Harriet.
Hi.
무슨 일이에요?
Everything okay?
죄송해요
너무 이른 건 알지만
I'm sorry, I know it's early.
요구르트 있으세요?
Do you have any yogurt?
슈퍼마켓 폭동 이후
식량이 다 없어져서
The food mart's emptied out
after the people raided it,
지금 안 토하는 음식이
요구르트밖에 없어요
and it's the only thing
I can keep down.
1달 남았죠?
Just a month to go, huh?
6주요
Six weeks.
제 남편 임무가
곧 끝나서
Greg's deployment
was gonna be over
아기가 태어날 때
집에 있기로 했었는데,
so he could be home
when the baby's born,
지금 돔 때문에...
but with this thing...
모르겠네요
I don't know.
안녕하세요
Oh. Hi.
좋은 아침입니다
Morning.
바비, 이 분은
제 이웃 해리엇이에요
Barbie, this is
my neighbor Harriet.
그리고 요구르트는 있어요
I think I have that yogurt.
죄송해요
I'm sorry.
어디가세요?
Where are you off to?
도망이라도 가시게요?
Running away?
어제 다들 제정신이 아니었고
Half the town
going nuts yesterday,
오늘도 또 그럴 수
있기 때문에...
that wasn't a fluke.
So...
린다나 도와주려 가려고요
Linda could still use my help.
내가 어젯 밤에
I told you last night
-앤지 손대지 말라고 했었지?
-죄송해요
to stay away from Angie, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
그냥 앤지한테
할 말이 있어서요
I... I went to her room
just to talk to her.
이러지 마세요
Please don't do this.
제발 이러지 마세요
Come on, please, don't.
쟤가 듣는다고요
She... she can hear.
지금 네 망신만 생각하냐?
Oh, I'm embarrassing you?
Huh?
-네가 쟤 감금했던 건 기억 안 나?
-어쩔수 없었어요
The guy who locks a girl up in a shelter?
I had to.
돔이 앤지를
미치게 했다고요
The dome was making her sick.
미친건 바로 너야!
You're the one who's sick!
그렇게 말하지 마세요
Please don't say that.
여기서 나가라
You have to leave.
여기가 제 집인데
저더러 어딜 가라고요?
This is my home.
Where else am I supposed to go?
여기만 들어오지 마라
Anywhere but here.
그리고 또 다시
앤지 해코지하려들면
And if you ever
so much as get near Angie,
후회하게 해 줄 거다
I'll make you sorry.
약속하는데
I promise.
아빠, 이러지 마요
Dad, don't.
쟨 정말 미쳤어요
He is crazy.
더 이상은 문제를
일으키지 않을 거다
Well, now he won't be a problem
for either of us.
피곤해 보이는구나
You look tired.
나도 그렇고
I know I am.
여기 머물어도 괜찮다
More than welcome to stay here.
아저씬 그냥 이 일을
You just want to make sure
제가 아무에게도
말 안하게 하려 그러시죠?
I don't tell everyone
what Junior did.
No, I...
아니요, 전...
지금 남동생한테 갈 거에요
I'm going home to my brother.
로즈 아줌마한테
작별인사하고요
After I say good-bye to Rose.
로즈 아줌마
어디에...
Where did, um...
...있으시죠?
...where's her body?
코긴스 목사 얘기
들었는지 모르겠구나
I don't know if you heard
about Lester Coggins,
그 분이 죽은 후로
영안실 관리를 안 하고 있다
but no one took over
the mortuary since he passed,
그래서 린다가 로즈를...
so Linda had to leave Rose...
그 식당에 그냥 두고 왔단다
in the Sweetbriar kitchen.
뭐라고요?
What?
그게 잘못됬다는 건 안다
I know it's a shame,
묻기 전까지만
거기에 둘 거야
but it's just until
she can get buried.
여기
Here.
열쇠가 있으니
보러 가거라
I want you to take this
and go see her.
식당 열쇠
아저씨가 갖고 갔어요?
You have a key to the diner?
그게 낫잖니
Well, I'd better.
그 식당은
내 소유란다
I own the place.
난 식당 개업이후로
계속 로즈에게 돈을 빌려줬었어
I kept loaning Rose money
over the years to keep it open.
얼마 후 그게
It just seemed silly
이상하게 생각되어서,
내가 샀단다
after a while,
so I... bought it.
아줌마가 아저씨
친구였단 것도 알아요
I know that she was
your friend, too.
로즈에게 내몫까지
작별인사를 해 주렴
Say good-bye for both of us.
정말 고마워요, 줄리아
Thanks again, Julia.
천만에요
Any time.
해리엇!
MAN:
Harriet!
자기야!
Honey!
이쪽으로 와
Come here.
그레이그?
Greg?
정말 당신이야?
You're really here?
자기 보려고
집으로 돌아왔어
I finally made it
home to you, baby.
(electrical crackling)
Ah!
(panting)
(groans)
그레이그?
Greg? Greg?
줄리아!
Julia!
-해리엇?
-줄리아!
JULIA: Harriet?
Julia!
누가 좀 도와줘요!
Anybody, help me, please!
가고 있어요!
Ah!
JULIA: I'm coming, sweetie.
저 왔어요
I got you.
I'm right here.
괜찮아요
(gasping)
It's okay. It's okay.
-양수가 터진 거에요
-안 돼!
It's just your water breaking.
No...
예정보다 너무 일러요!
It's too early!
돔을 건드렸는데...
Ah...
I touched the dome.
제...
I...
제 아기에게
무슨 일이
I think it did something
생겼나봐요
to my baby.
(groaning)
Under The Dome
Season 1 Episode 7
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Imperfect Circle
결함
문제가 있나요?
JUNIOR:
Something wrong?
너 이제는 출근하는 것도
귀찮아하는 모습이다
You're the only deputy
that bothered to show up today.
어디로 순찰 갈까요?
Where else am I gonna go?
주니어
BARBIE:
Junior.
이봐요
Hey.
다음에는 이 마을에
Anyone else wondering
어떤 일이 벌어질지
짐작가는 사람 있어요?
what's gonna happen
next in this town?
던디 형제 잡아야죠
Yeah, well, we need
to deal with the Dundees.
클린트랑 웨일런이
어제 로즈를 죽였잖아요
Clint and Waylon
killed Rose yesterday.
어젯 밤 걔네 집에 갔었는데
I went by their
place last night,
집에는 안 갔더라고요
but they're smart enough
not to go home.
걔네를 잡읍시다
Let's go track 'em down.
주니어, 넌
계속 순찰을 돌아
Junior, you stay on patrol.
누가 또 가게 물건을
If someone even looks like
도둑질 할 거 같으면,
가게를 폐쇄해버려
they're even thinking of
looting, you shut it down.
바비를 순찰 돌게 시켜요
Okay, just let him go on patrol.
전 던디 형제를 알기 때문에
말로 진정시킬 수 있다고요
I know the Dundees; I might
be able to talk them down
without things getting stupid.
전 괜찮습니다
Uh, that's fine by me.
알겠어, 따라와
All right, come on.
(gasps)
Okay.
고마워요, 줄리아
Thank you, Julia.
(sighs)
그레이그를 봤다고요?
You thought you saw Greg?
정말로 봤어요
I did see Greg.
제게 손인사도 했다고요
He was waving to me.
그래서 돔이
사라진 줄 알았어요
I thought it meant
that the dome was gone,
그런데 제가
남편을 만지려고 하는 순간
and then when I went to him
and tried to touch him...
-사라졌군요
-진작에 제가
He wasn't there.
I should've known
그게 사실이 아닌 걸...
it was too good to be...
(gasps, groans)
병동으로 가 봐야 겠어요
We should get you
to the clinic.
제 차를 타고 가요
Okay, let's take my car.
병원에서 받은 물건들도
차에 있어요
Greg put a hospital
go bag in there.
알겠어요
Okay.
가요
Let's go.
(doorbell jingles)
로즈
Rose.
안에 누구죠?
BEN:
Who's in there?!
저리 가!
Stay away from me!
Whoa, whoa!
해치려는 게 아니에요
I'm not gonna hurt you.
저기
Wait.
조 누나 아니세요?
You're Joe's sister.
전 조 친구
벤이에요
I'm Ben. I'm friends
with your brother.
조는 괜찮아?
Uh, is Joe okay?
걔 여친이랑
데이트 중이에요
Yeah, he's hanging
with his new girlfriend.
그 칼 내려놓아도 되요
Seriously, you don't need
to be stabby with me.
문이 열려있길래
또 누가 식당 물건을
I just saw the door open
and wanted to make sure
부수고 있는 건 아닌지
확인하려던 거였어요
no one was
wrecking stuff again.
(exhales)
맙소사
Oh, damn.
로즈 아줌마죠?
Is that Rose?
나 좀 도와줄래?
Will you help me
with something?
다 넉넉히 가져가세요
OLLIE: Go on, folks,
take all you can carry.
저 우물은 쉽게
마르지 않을 겁니다
That well ain't running
out any time soon.
사업이 번창하고 있구만
BIG JIM:
So business is booming.
아주 입이 찢어질 정도로
웃고 있구만
That grin of yours is about
to cut the top of your head off.
마을이 날
필요로 하잖나
Well, town needed me.
도움을 줄 수 있어
기쁘다네
And I'm happy to help.
그러시겠지
Sure you are.
내가 자네에게 프로판을
계속 준다면 말일세
Long as I keep you
stockpiled in propane.
난 자본주의자거든
Just a capitalist.
꼭 자네처럼 말일세
Like you, Jim.
그런데 자네 나랑 수다나 떨려고
여기 온 건 아니겠지
But you didn't come
out here to chew the fat
with your old pal.
아닐세
No.
자네랑 화해하려고 온 거네
I came to bury the hatchet.
자네가?
You?
이봐, 올리
Look, Ollie.
계속 서로에게
못되게 하는 거보단
We can keep pissing
each other off
힘을 합치는 게 낫지 않겠나
or we can get things done.
자네에겐 물이 있고,
Okay? Now, you got the water.
나한텐 프로판이 있지
I got lots of propane.
우리가 협력한다면,
마을 상황을 좋게 만들 수 있네
We work together, we can get
this town here back on track,
주민 모두가
자립하게 할 수도 있을 거야
and our friends and neighbors
back on their feet.
친절하신 양반이구만
Good old Big Jim.
항상 마을을 생각하고 말야
Always thinking
of Chester's Mill.
그게 옳은 일이잖나
Well, it's
the right thing to do.
그런데...
Still...
프로판 공급은
확실한 건가?
you sure about that
propane supply?
절대 떨어지지 않을 걸세
Trust me, it won't run out.
그거야 물론 그렇겠지
Oh, I don't doubt that.
내 말은... 프로판이
여전히 자네 거라고 생각하나?
But what I'm asking is...
are you sure it's still yours?
그게 무슨 뜻이지?
What the hell does that mean?
체스터스 밀에서의
또다른 상쾌한 아침이 왔다네
Sure was a nice new dawn
this morning, wasn't it?
(electrical crackling)
뭐 느껴졌어?
Anything?
응
Yeah.
너 키스 정말 잘한다
You're really good at that.
돔 관련해서 말이야
From the dome, Joe.
돔한테서 뭐 안 느껴졌어?
Anything from the dome?
발작 같은 건
전혀 느껴지지 않았는데
I didn't feel anything,
like a seizure.
나도
Me neither.
안타깝지만
Unfortunately.
우리가 헛다리를
짚었었나봐
Maybe we're going
about it all wrong.
돔에 손을 대 보고,
I-I mean, we've touched it.
돔에 말도 걸어 보고
We've talked to it.
-돔에서 너랑 사랑도 나눠 보고
-끝내줬지
Made out on it.
Which was awesome.
아마 우리가 뭔가
색다른 걸 할 때마다
But every single time
something has happened,
돔에서 이상한 일이
생기는 것 같아
it's been because we did
something different.
그래서 돔 위에서
섹스라도 해 보자구?
Joe, I'm not
having sex with you
for the first time
against the dome.
그런 뜻은 아니었어
I didn't mean that.
너 혹시...
하고 싶어?
Wait, but...
you want to do that?
정신 차리셔
Focus.
내 말은...
I'm just saying.
우리가 잘못된 장소에서
Maybe we're trying
to get a response
이러고 있는지도 몰라
from it in the wrong place.
중요한 곳은
돔 경계선이 아닐 수도 있잖아
Maybe the real action isn't
along the perimeter.
그럼 어딜까?
(whimpers)
Where else would it be?
만약 돔이
원자와 유사한 구조라면,
If the dome is like an atom,
이 장벽은 전자 역할을
하고 있는 걸 거야
and these walls are-are
just electrons...
그 말은 마을 중심에
원자핵이 있다는 거지
...that means there has to be
a nucleus in the center of it.
그게 돔을 여기에
묶어두고 있는 거야
Which could be holding
it all together.
마을 중심으로
가 봐야겠어
Maybe that's where we should go.
넌 정말 똑똑해
조 매컬리스터
You're smart, Joe McAlister.
(barking)
이게 다 뭔가, 부머?
What the hell is this, Boomer?
옥수수밭 가는 길에
You better say
you somehow got lost
길이라도 잃은 건가?
on your way
to your damn cornfield!
거기서 그만 두게, 레니
Gonna have to stop you
right there, Mr. Rennie.
올리가 아무도
출입시키지 말라고
Ollie says no one's allowed
-내게 말했네
-올리가?
inside but him.
Ollie?
-그래
-이건 내 거잖아
Yeah.
This is my property,
내 마음이라고!
I'll do whatever I please!
그 열쇠는 더 이상
쓸모 없을 걸세
Them keys ain't gonna
do you any good.
내 말 들어, 부머
Now, look here, Boomer.
여기서 당장 안 꺼지면...
You get out of my way...
(grunts)
이 자식...
You...
입만 산 개자식 같은 놈이...
Mouthy townie bastard.
(sighs)
(engine starts)
던디 형제를 잡아서
어떻게 할 거에요?
So what happens
after we catch Waylon and Clint?
감옥에 넣어야지
Put them in a cell.
그 다음에는요?
Then what?
지방 법원은
돔 밖에 있잖아요
I mean, county court's in
Westlake outside of the dome.
일단 놈들을 잡은 다음에
생각해 보자
We bring them in, and
then we figure it out.
로즈를 죽이고도 빠져나가게
내버려둘 순 없어
Dundees can't just walk
free after killing Rose.
앤지에게 하려던 짓도 있고
Or what they were
gonna do to Angie.
걔들이 앤지도 해쳤어요?
Wait, Angie was attacked?
다행히 무사하긴 해
Just so you know, she's okay.
걔들이 앤지를
강간하려 했어
They were gonna rape her.
다행히 바비가 왔지만,
놈들은 도망쳤지
Barbie stopped them,
but then they got away.
이번엔 도망치지 못할 거에요
Yeah, they won't
get away this time.
좀 더 빨리 가면 안 돼요?
Can you go faster?
좀만 더 가면 되요
It's just a few more blocks.
이건 또 뭐야?
What the hell is this?
제가 내려서...
Sorry, I got to...
(gunshot)
움직이지 마!
(screams)
Nobody move!
움직이면 쏜다!
Or I'll blow your head off!
맙소사, 어떡해요?
(gasps) My God, what do we do?
일단 얘네가
시키는 대로 해요
We do exactly what they say.
닥쳐!
Shut up!
됐어?
You got it?
자동차 기름을
털어가다니
I can't believe
we're being gas-jacked.
기름이 없으면
차는 쓸모가 없잖아요
Car's not nearly as useful
as the fuel.
야, 서둘러!
Come on, hurry up!
웨일런, 서두르라고!
Waylon, it's going!
Move!
(grunts)
(yelling)
린다?
BARBIE:
Linda?
린다, 바비에요
Linda, it's Barbie.
던디 놈들이랑
마주쳤어요
I just tangled
with the Dundees.
위치가 어디에요?
Copy. Where?
제 손을 꼭 쥐세요
(Harriet screams)
JULIA: Try and squeeze my hand.
(gunshot)
(grunts)
괜찮아요
아무도 안 다쳤어요
He's okay. No one's hurt.
He's okay.
마을 중심에 있어요
북쪽으로 도망가고 있어요
We're at town center.
They took off to the northwest.
산기가 있어요
LINDA: We're on it.
She's going into labor.
병동으로 데려가야 해요
We got to get her
to the clinic.
지금은 안 돼요
BARBIE: That's not
gonna happen.
-지금 병동이 닫혀 있어요
-애가 나와요!
Just went by there. It's closed.
My baby's coming!
앨리스
Alice.
앨리스가 의사에요
She's a doctor.
조네 집에서
묵고 있어요
She's staying
with Joe McAlister.
-가야 돼요
-그런데 지금 기름을 털려가지고
We got to go.
But this car's not going anywhere now.
그럼 걸어가요
서둘러요
Then let's start
walking, come on.
차 밖으로 꺼내요
어서요
Get her out of there, let's go.
어서
(groans)
Come on.
던디 놈들이
어디로 갔을 것 같아?
Where do you think Waylon
and Clint are headed?
북쪽으로 갔다면 아마도
Not much northwest of town.
폐차장에 갔을 거에요
Except that salvage yard.
어렸을 때 거기서
What, you never played
숨바꼭질도 안 해보셨어요?
hide and go seek
there as a kid?
낡은 건물들이 많고
It's got lots of old buildings.
주위엔 아무도 없거든요
No one around.
도망 중이기 때문에
거기로 갔을 거에요
If they're on the run,
they're probably there.
-가 봐야 겠네
-네
It's worth a shot.
Yeah.
가서 면상을 한 방
먹여주자고요
Let's go kick their teeth in.
그러면 안 돼
Like hell.
체포할 때 공식적인
절차를 밟아야 해
We're gonna arrest them and
read them their rights.
진심이에요?
What, seriously?
우린 자경단이 아니잖아
We're not vigilantes, okay?
우리 목숨이 위험할 때만
무기를 사용해야 돼
You only use that gun if
your life is in danger.
알아듣겠어?
Do you understand?
네, 알겠어요
Yeah, I got it.
당신이 보안관이니까요
Whatever you say, Sheriff.
(barking)
가까워지는 거 같아?
Do you think we're
getting closer?
돔 경계에서
8km 정도고
About five miles from the wall.
정남쪽으로 가는 중이니까
We've been going
perfectly southwest.
거의 왔을 거야
Shouldn't be too far now.
여기서 나가게 되면
If we ever get out of here,
너 지도제작이라도
한 번 해봐라
you should seriously
consider a career
in cartography.
돔 데이날 벤이랑 같이
지도를 그렸었어
Me and Ben mapped
the dome on day one.
삼각함수 수업을
열심히 듣었길 다행이지
Lucky I paid attention
in trig class.
이걸 없앤다면,
인슐린도 넉넉히 구할 수 있을 텐데
If we turn it off,
we can get my mom more insulin.
엄마는 어떠셔?
H-How is she?
괜찮으신데, 인슐린은
더 필요해
She's good, but we're
gonna need more.
조?
Joe?
왜 돔이 우리를 선택했을까
생각해 봤어?
Do you ever wonder
why it picked us?
응, 돔이 우릴 택해서
난 정말 좋아
Sure, but I'm mainly
just glad it did.
뭐라구?
Excuse me?
내 말은, 물론
무섭고 이상하긴 하지만
I mean, it's weird
and it's scary,
이 일은 지구 역사상
처음 있는 일이잖아
but it's the first time anything
like this has happened on Earth.
그런 면에서
That's awesome...
진짜 경탄할 만한
사건이잖아
in the true "awe"
sense of awesome.
더욱이 만약
돔이 없었다면
Uh, not to mention,
if it hadn't come down,
난 너를 만나지도 못했을테고
I might not have met you.
(Truman barking)
쟤 왜 저러지?
What's his problem?
트루먼!
Truman!
괜찮아?
Are you okay?
트루먼?
Truman?
(whimpering)
트루먼!
Truman!
뭔가 잘못 된걸
느꼈나봐
He thinks something's wrong.
돌아가야 될까?
Should we go back, too?
여기서 멈출 순 없어
We can't stop now.
거의 다 왔잖아
We're close.
(doorbells jingle)
누군가를 묻은 경험은
오늘이 처음이야
Man, I never buried
anyone before.
엉망이 된 것 같아
That was messed up.
좋은 일이긴 하지만
I mean it was nice.
넌 정말 좋은 일을 한 거야
It was nice of you
to bury Rose.
(sighs)
난 평소에 아줌마를
고맙게 여기지 않았어
I never appreciated her.
난...
I...
항상 너무 바빠서
다른 곳에서 살길 바랬어
was always too busy wishing
that I was somewhere else.
다른 사람으로 살길 바랬어
Someone else.
여길 청소해야 돼
We got to clean this place up.
안에 걸레 있는지 좀 봐 줄래?
Why don't you go see if
you can find us a mop.
(doorbells jingle)
왜 다치셨어요?
What happened to you?
사람들이 문제를
일으키고 있어
People making trouble
for themselves.
술이 필요해
I need a drink.
이야!
BEN:
Hell yeah!
원샷이네요!
Chug!
친구랑 같이 있는줄
몰랐네, 앤지
Didn't know
you had company, Angie.
밴 드레이크에요
BEN:
Ben Drake, sir.
주니어 경기 때
만난 적 있잖아요
We met at one of Junior's games.
주니어 얘기 하고 있었니?
You been talking about Junior?
아니요
ANGIE:
No.
피 닦아 놓거라
Clean this blood up.
자기야, 말했잖아
Babe, I told you,
나 훨씬 좋아졌어
I'm feeling much better.
지금이야 그렇겠지만
For now.
진짜로 아프기 전엔
엄살떨고 싶진 않아
I just don't want to act sick
until I am sick.
-자기야...
-부탁이야
Honey...
Please?
인슐린 투여가
불규칙적이잖아
Your insulin has been
so irregular.
문제를 일으킬 수가 있어
It has to be messing with you.
정말 이러지 않아도 돼
I'm telling you,
I don't need this.
알겠다
이 나쁜 것
Okay then, badass.
일어나서 춤이나 추자
Get up and dance.
그래
I want to.
시간이 없어요
♪ No time
미안해
I'm sorry.
뭐가?
For what?
여기로 오자고 해서
For bringing us here.
노리를 캠프에
데려가자고 해서 말야
For insisting that Norrie
be sent to that program.
나도 동의했잖아
I insisted, too.
그리고 난 너를
어디든지 따라갈거야
And I would
follow you anywhere.
누구의 잘못도 아니야
It is no one's fault.
앨리스?
(knocking)
JULIA: Alice?
제 이웃 해리엇이에요
It's my neighbor Harriet.
지금 산기가 있어요
She's in labor a month early.
소파로 데려가요
(panting)
Let's get her on the couch.
Oh...
좋아요, 부드럽고...
All right, nice and...
부드럽고 천천히
nice and slow.
-해리엇?
-네?
Harriet?
Yeah.
-전 앨리스 캘버트에요
-가지 마요...
I am Alice Calvert...
Don't leave.
안가요... 괜찮으실 거에요
I'm not leaving.
...and you are gonna be just fine.
돔 안에서 첫번째로 태어난
아기를 갖게 되겠네요
Actually, you're gonna have the
first baby born inside the dome.
(chuckles)
이런
Oh, my God.
팔에 닭살이 돋았어
The hair's standing up
on my arms.
저기 있다
And there it is.
저게 뭐지?
NORRIE:
What the hell is that?
(electrical buzz)
충격이 왔어
It shocked me.
(electrical buzz)
이건 말도 안 돼
You've got to be kidding me.
또 다른 돔이라고?
Another dome?
안에 뭔가가 있는 것 같아
I think there's
something inside.
(gasps)
현재 10cm에요
힘을 줄 때에요
(screams)
Ten centimeters. It's almost time to push.
남편이 있어야 돼요
I can't do this
without my husband.
-아님 못해요
-해리엇, 내 말 들어요
(crying): I can't.
Harriet. Harriet, listen to me.
-못 해요
-이건 흔히 있는 일이에요
I can't do this.
This happens every day.
하실 수 있어요
You can do this.
이건 흔히 있는 일이
아니에요, 앨리스
This is not every day, Alice.
이럴 때 이렇게...
This isn't right...
(sobs)
...애를 낳는 건
옳지 못해요
...bringing someone
into a world like this.
(sobbing)
해리엇,당신은
훌륭한 엄마가 될 거에요
Harriet, you are gonna
be a wonderful mother.
우리 처음 만났을 때
기억해요?
Do you remember
when we first met?
초음파 사진 보여주시면서
엄청 좋아했잖아요
You showed me the sonogram, and
you couldn't contain yourself.
이런 시기에는
희망이 없어요
There's no hope
with people behaving this way.
점점 상황이
악화만 되어 가요
And it's only gonna
get worse, isn't it?
다 같이 여기에
갇혔잖아요, 안 그래요?
With all of us trapped
under this thing? Isn't it?
-그렇게 생각 마요
-이봐요, 해리엇
JULIA: You don't know that.
Okay, Harriet, Harriet, Harriet.
절 보세요
절 봐봐요
Look at me.
좋은 일도 일어나고 있어요
Good things happened today.
항상 도움을 주는
좋은 사람들도 있어요
Right? Some people,
they're always gonna show up.
우리도 여기 있고요
Now, we're here.
알겠어요?
우린 아무데도 안 가요
All right?
We're not going anywhere,
그렇지만 당신도
힘을 내야 해요
but I'm gonna need you
to show up, too.
-알겠어요?
-네
Okay?
(sobs) Okay.
알겠죠?
Yeah?
네
제 손 좀 잡아주실래요?
Okay.
Will you hold my hand?
잡았어요, 알겠죠?
Listen, I got you. Okay?
우리 다 여기 있어요
We all do.
해리엇, 셋을 세면
힘을 줘요
ALICE: Harriet, it's
time to push, on three.
할 수 있어요, 해리엇
하나...
You can do this,
Harriet. One...
둘...
(gasps)
two...
셋!
three!
(knocks)
이봐, 짐
OLLIE:
Hey, Jimmy.
프로판 창고지기랑
I hear you had
a little run-in
작은 싸움이 있었다고 들었는데
with the new security guard
at your old propane warehouse.
작은 싸움
이상이었지
Had worse.
나도 내 오랜 친구 짐이
살찐 고양이처럼 여기 틀어박혀서
Well, I hate to see
my old friend sittin' here,
상처나 치료하고 있단 사실이
슬프구만
licking his wounds
like a fat-ass cat.
그러니 간단히 얘기하지
So I'll be brief.
아침에 나랑 협력하자고 했었지
Earlier, you said we
should be working together.
그렇지만
우물도 내 거고
But you see, I got the well.
이게 틀린 말이 아니라면,
And unless I'm wrong,
내가 자네보다
농작물도 많이 가지고 있고
I got more crops
than you townies,
프로판 가스도
내 거가 되었지
and now I got the propane.
그러니 자네가 그토록
아끼는 이 마을이
So unless you want
your beloved Chester's Mill
굶어죽지 않게 하려면...
to starve to death...
내 말을 잘 들어야 할 거야
you'll toe the line.
이제 내가 흘린 땀이
마을에 도움을 줄 때가 되었네
You see, it's my turn
to have my sweaty hand
wrapped around this town's neck.
그러니 이제부턴,
So from now on,
내가 점프하라고 명령하면,
when I say "Jump,"
얼마나 높이 점프해야 할지
궁리해야 할 걸세
you say, "How high?"
내가 상쾌한 아침이 밝았다고
했던 말 기억하지
Didn't I say it was
a nice new dawn this morning?
여기선 아무도 안 보여, 그 쪽 어때?
I don't see anybody, do you?
왜 그렇게 쫄아있어?
What are you so scared of?
어제 널 죽이려고 했던
남자 말이야
Uh, the guy that kicked
your ass yesterday.
오늘 또 우릴 공격했잖아
Almost did it again today.
경관인 거 같던데
I think he's a deputy.
-린다에게 말했을 거 같아
-경관이 우리를
You know he's gonna tell Linda.
You know, they ought
신경써야 돼
우리가 경관을 신경쓰는 게 아니라
to worry about us,
not the other way around.
마을이 박살나고 있다고, 클린트
Whole town's
falling apart, Clint.
이렇게 기회가 많을 때
기회를 이용해야 돼
There's a lot of good
opportunities, going forward.
웨일런
(whispering):
Waylon.
그쪽에 누가 있어
There's somebody on your side.
클린트, 이 개자식아
Damn, you're stupid, Clint.
총 버리고
손을 볼 수 있게 들어!
Drop 'em and put your hands
where I can see them!
말 들어
Do what he says.
당장!
Now!
손 머리 뒤로 해
Put your hands
behind your head.
너희 둘을
로즈 트위첼
You're both under arrest
살해 혐의로 체포한다
for the murder
of Rose Twitchell.
묵비권을 행사할
권리가 있으며
You have the right
to remain silent.
지금 하는 말은 법정에서
불리하게 적용될 수 있고...
Anything you say
can and will be held against...
(grunts)
제발
Please.
조용히 따라갈게
(panting):
I'll go quietly, please.
순순히 따라갈게
I'll go peacefully.
제발...
Please...
(gunshot)
주니어...
Junior...
체포했습니다
Got him.
이게 돔의 발생장치인지도 몰라
Maybe it's the generator
that created the whole dome.
열려라
Open.
꺼져라
Open and turn off.
프로그램 종료
End program.
안 먹히는데
It's not working, Joe.
그런 것 같아?
You think?
안녕하세요
Hello.
대화를 시작합니다
Begin communication.
누구한테 말하는 거야?
Who are you talking to?
야, 거기!
Hey, you!
대화를 시작한다고!
Initiate communication!
소리지르는 걸
싫어하는지도 몰라
Maybe it doesn't like
being yelled at.
예의바르게 해보는 건 어때?
What if we ask nicely?
우리가 동시에 닿았을 때
큰 돔이 응답했었잖아
The big dome responded when
we both touched it together,
라디오도 작동시켰고
and made the radio work again.
(electrical buzzing)
알겠어
Okay.
정체는 모르겠지만,
Outer space thing,
당신하고 대화하게 해 준다면
we would like it very much
정말로 감사하겠어요
if we could just talk to you.
-또...
-노리
And...
Norrie.
엄마?
Mom?
엄마를 찾아봐야겠어
I need to find my mom.
어서!
Come on!
됐어요! 됐어요!
(screams)
That's it! That's it!
좋아요
(groans)
That's great.
됐어요
Okay.
(exhales)
Uh-oh.
왜 그래요?
아기한테 문제 있어요?
What?
Is something wrong
with my baby?
아니요, 괜찮아요
No, you're fine, sweetheart.
뭔가 이상해
(whispers):
Something's wrong.
앨리스?
Alice?
Uh...
(groans softly)
무슨 일이죠?
What's happening?
다 괜찮아요
알겠죠?
Nothing.
Everything's fine, okay?
계속 힘주고 계세요
You got to keep pushing,
all right?
-아니...
-힘 주고 계세요
No, I... (crying)
Yes. Yes, all right?
셋에 힘 줘요
알겠죠?
Push on three. Ready?
-하나... 힘 주세요, 하나...
-너무 아파요
One... Here we go. One...
It hurts so much.
...둘, 셋
지금이요!
...two, three.
Push!
♪
(quiet rustling)
(gunshots)
(yells)
안 돼! 안 돼!
No! No!
(groaning)
다 됐어요
머리가 나왔어요
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Head's out.
다... 다 괜찮은 거예요?
I don't... is this...
is everything all right here?
안 돼, 안 돼
No. No, no, no.
-그러지 마
-도와줘야 돼
You can't.
I have to.
알겠어...
Okay...
지금 힘 주시면 안 돼요
I need you to stop pushing.
Uh...
해리엇, 힘 그만 주세요
Harriet, you need
to stop pushing.
-네?
-그만 하셔야 돼요
What?
I need you to stop pushing.
탯줄이...
The cord...
탯줄이 아기 목을
감고 있어요
it's wrapped around
the baby's neck.
젠장, 그럼 어떻게 할지
설명해주시겠어요?
(sighs) Okay, well, you're gonna
have to walk me through this.
탯줄을 잘라내야 돼요
All right?
You have to cut the cord so the baby
-숨 쉴 수 있게요
-알겠어요
can breathe.
BARBIE: Okay.
탯줄을 죄어서,
Clamp it.
-뭘로요?
-끈으로요
With what?
Uh, a string.
-서둘러요
-끈이요
Hurry. I got it.
BARBIE: A string, yeah.
-아기 좀 제발 살려줘요!
-해리엇...
Somebody help my baby!
ALICE: Harriet...
힘만 주지 말고 있어요
just don't push yet.
신발끈을 찾았어요
I found shoelaces.
서둘러요
Hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry, hurry.
두 방향으로 묶어서
Tie it off in two places.
-여기요
-됐어요, 됐어요
This one.
I got it, I got it.
-네, 그거요
-됐어요
Yeah. That's it.
Okay, I got that.
되고 있어요
괜찮아요?
I'm good, I'm good.
You?
괜찮아요
JULIA:
Yeah.
자, 다 됐습니다
Yeah? Okay, here we go.
(panting)
됐어요
(scissors snip)
Okay.
좋아요
탯줄을 잘랐습니다
Great.
All right, cord's cut.
해리엇, 다시 힘을 줘요
Okay, Harriet,
you can push now.
마지막으로
One last
있는 힘껏이요
알겠죠?
big push.
Come on, one more. Okay?
-지금요?
-셋을 세면요, 하나...
Push now?
On three. One...
둘...셋,
지금이요!
two... three. Push!
밀어요, 밀어요
Push, push, push,
push, push, push...
밀어요, 밀어요
(groaning)
push, push, push, push, push, push.
Oh!
(baby crying)
예쁜 딸을 나으셨네요
You've got
a beautiful baby girl.
정말 예뻐요!
There she is!
Look at her, look at her.
내 딸...
Oh, my...
엄마 보러 가자
BARBIE:
Let's go see Mama.
꽉 감싸요
Swaddle her up.
다 됐습니다
There we go.
정말...
Oh, my...
(crying)
(laughing)
정말 예뻐요
해리엇
JULIA:
She's beautiful, Harriet.
내 딸...
Oh, my lamb.
(Julia laughs)
Oh.
안녕
Hello.
고마워요
Thank you.
안아봐도 돼요?
May I?
물론이요
(cries) Of course.
착하지
Shh. That's good.
조심하세요
Oh, yeah.
Be careful.
여기요
Here she is.
(cooing)
안녕
Hi.
앨리스...
Alice....
애 이름을
앨리스로 해야겠어요
...meet Alice.
고마워요
Thank you.
엄마한테 다시 가자
Oh, let's go back
and see Mama, huh?
이리 와라
(stifled groaning)
Come here, you.
Oh, oh, oh.
애도 오늘
힘들었을거야
JULIA:
She's a little traveler already.
됐어요
BARBIE:
There we go.
앨리스?
(Alice groans)
Alice?
앨리스? 앨리스?
(grunting, gasping)
Alice? Alice?
앨리스?
BARBIE:
Alice?
앨리스!
Alice!
앨리스, 왜 그래요?
BARBIE:
Alice, what's wrong?
가슴이...
H... heart...
앨리스...
CAROLYN:
Alice...
왜 그래요?
(gasps)
BARBIE: What's wrong?
오늘 도와줘서 고마워, 벤
I appreciate
your help today, Ben.
Hmm.
왜 그렇게 웃어요?
What are you smiling about?
이 식당 안에서
기분 좋게 일한 건
I just realized that
this is the first time
오늘이 처음인 것 같아
I've ever worked here and
not been pissed off about it.
안녕, 앤지
Hi, Angie.
왜 그래, 난 널...
(gasping) Come on, I'm...
안 해칠 거야
not gonna bite you.
너네 아빠 말씀
기억 안 나?
Your dad told you
to leave me alone.
할 말이 있어서 그래
I just need
to tell you something.
넌 집에 가도 돼
So you can go home.
아니, 계속 있을 건데
Nah, man, I don't think I will.
(laughs)
Um...
네가 나를 사랑하게
만들 수 없다는 걸 깨달았어
I just wanted to tell you
that I know
I can't make you love me.
내 실수였지
That was my mistake.
미안하단 말을 하고 싶었어
I just want you to know
that I'm sorry.
다 미안해
For everything.
알겠어
Fine.
사과했으니,
You said it.
이제 가 봐
Now leave.
그리고 던디 형제 말이야
Oh, and, uh, those Dundee guys?
다신 널 괴롭히지 못할 거야
They'll never bother you again.
이게 다야
That's all.
잘 들어가
Good night.
(door opens)
(door closes)
오늘 정말 멋지셨어요
That was pretty amazing
what you did.
(door opens)
(door closes)
엄마 어딨어요?
Where's my mom?
윗층에 있다
Upstairs.
심장마비였대
She said it was a heart attack.
뭐라고?
What?
순환계에 큰 무리가 온 모양이야
Her system's just been
through way too much.
엄마, 나 왔어
Mom, I'm here.
(sighs)
노리야
Elinore.
(sighs)
우리 아기
Baby girl.
조!
ANGIE:
Joe!
(sighs)
진짜 오랜만이다, 짜식아
Long time no see,
you little brat.
고맙다
Thanks, man.
천만에
No problem.
괜찮아?
You all right?
누난 괜찮아?
Are you okay?
응
Yeah.
너가 때맞춰 와서...
So...
정말 좋구나
glad you made it.
뭔가 잘못된 걸 알았어
I knew something was wrong.
어떻게?
How?
숲속에서 엄마를 봤어
I saw you in the woods.
돔이 그러길 원했던 거 같아
It was like the
dome wanted me to.
미친 소리 같지만
I sound crazy.
마을 전체가 미쳤는데 뭘
It's all crazy.
다른 분 아기 낳는 걸...
I helped...
내가 도와줬단다
a woman give birth.
그 분도...
She said...
돔이 자기 남편을
보게 해 줬대
the dome made her
see her husband.
그리고 태어난
아기 이름이 앨리스야
And now there's
a new Alice here.
이 일들이...
It all...
중요한 거란다
must matter.
아니,
엄마도 중요해
No, Mom. You matter, too.
돔이 널 여기로 데려왔다면,
ALICE:
But if it brought you here,
난 떠날 운명인 것 같구나
it must want me to go.
아니야
No.
적어도 돔이...
At least...
우리 예쁜 딸을...
it let me see my beautiful...
한 번 더 보게 해 줬구나
...baby girl
one last time.
너랑 캐럴린...
You and Carolyn...
서로 잘 보살펴주렴
take care of each other.
엄마는 아무데도 안 갈거야
Mom, you're not going anywhere.
가야 돼
But I am.
그러니...
So...
용감해지거라
you have to be brave.
알겠어
(crying):
Okay.
정말로, 약속할게
I will. I promise.
사랑한다
Love... you.
정말 사랑해, 엄마
I love you so much, Mom.
(sobbing softly)
노리?
Nore?
노리!
Norrie!
가 봐
Go.
(crying)
엄마를 살려 내
Bring her back.
원하는 건 다 해 줄테니까
I'll do anything you want.
원하는 게 뭔지 말해보라고
Just tell me what you want.
제발 엄마만 데려가지 마!
Don't take her away from me!
♪
그대의
♪ Send
꿈을
♪ Your
보내요
♪ Dreams
아무도 없는 곳으로
♪ Where nobody hides
그대의
♪ Give
눈물을
♪ Your
바치세요
♪ Tears
바다에게
♪ To the tide
(sniffles)
시간이 없어요
♪ No time
♪ No time.
(crying)
원하는 게 뭔지 말해 보라고!
Just tell me what you want!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
한글자막 by 뒷북()
DC인사이드
기타 미국드라마 갤러리